Hello guys welcome to another video of stock
market friends III Lombard General
Insurance Limited has
presented its December quarter financial results.
In today's video we
will analyze both the third quarter and nine month
hand results of the company have been out.
We will cover them in this video today.
Friends let's start the video. So guys
we have come here, see the results, the
numbers are in lax and this portion is of
quarter ended, this is of nine months ended
and this is the results of the last financial year.
We will cover the quarterly
income of the company this time. The total income is Rs
5003 crore, in the previous quarter it was Rs 5049
crore and in the December 22 quarter it is Rs 4362
crore. The income is down quarter on quarter
but has increased year on year
and if we talk about the expenses, then the
total expenses of the company,
if seen, the total expenses of the company
here is Rs
4587 crore in the last quarter.  4452
crores and in the December 22 quarter there was an
expense of 4855 crores. There is an
increase in the quarter on quarter but
if seen year on year then there is a huge
increase. See here, there is a
downfall in the quarter on quarter income but
the expenses have increased due to which the
profit this time if seen, the operating
profit which has come out is 4159 crores.
In the previous quarter it was 597 crores and
in the December 22 quarter the
operating profit is 2764 crores. It is
down quarter on quarter and
increased year on year and the
reason for the downfall in quarter on quarter is the
downfall in the income and increase in the expenses.
If we look at its net profit
before tax here, then the
profit before tax of the company is ₹73.7 crores
in the previous quarter and ₹7636 crores
in the December 22 quarter. The operating profit is ₹465 crores. It is
down quarter on quarter and has
increased year on year. Here the profit of the
company is  Provision had to be paid
for tax, provision
of 142 crores had to be paid, 186 crores in the previous quarter
and 11.7 crores in the December 22 quarter,
quarter
on quarter it is down, year on year the
net profit of the
company has increased, if we
see the net profit this time then Guy company has a
net profit of 4 sorry 431 crores,
in the previous quarter it was 577 crores, in the December 22
quarter it is 3525 crores,
quarter on quarter it is down, year
on year it has increased, whereas if we
see the dividend etc. of Guys company here this time, the dividend of ₹ is
shown here, a dividend of ₹ has been paid in this quarter,
but right now when the
dividend of the company will be paid,
it has not been told here,
but it has not been announced in the result,
if we talk about EPS, then the dividend
of the company  The EPS is 8.73, it is
down quarter on quarter and has increased year on year. So
guys,
if we look at the overall result of the company, it is average. The reason is
that the company's income is down quarter on
quarter, plus the expenses have also increased a lot,
due to which the profit is
down, but the income has increased year on year
and the expenses have also increased here,
but the profit has also increased here, so we
can say that the average result of the company has been done. So
now we
end the video here. If someone
asks in the comment box, we will meet next time, we will talk about it before that. You
can see the company here and we will meet in the
next video till then bye bye.